You mean it had not started after the lapse of time.
Actually.
Is it starting? Can you hear me? Gentlemen.
Can you?
Good evening.
Am I doing well?
I don't know.
Good evening.
Can you hear me? Has it started?
Has it started?
Has it begun?
Yes, that's the tone.
It sounds like they're coming,
Has it started?
Oh, here it comes.
Thank God. It's started.
Good evening.
Can you hear me?
I think I can hear you.
So, once again, good evening everyone.
It's our Battention's Time!
Yes, it is. So, I've made a sudden announcement today,
So, I have to make a sudden announcement today,
I, Sakura Seta, will graduate from Batten Shoujo-tai on December 7th,
I, Sakura Seta, will graduate from "Batten Shoujo-tai" on December 7, and I will be leaving StanDust Promotion at the end of December.
Yes, well, I would like to tell you about the background and so on,
I would like to start by telling you about the background and my feelings.
Thank you very much for gathering here today, as well as the members.
I think I have surprised you.
That's right.
I've been thinking a lot about this presentation and so on for the past several years,
I have been thinking about this announcement and other things for the past several years,
I have been thinking about this announcement and other things over the past few years, and I have been feeling uneasy,
I felt like I was missing something,
I was thinking slowly, but that's how I felt,
I was thinking about it slowly, and that's how I felt, so I think everyone is going to be very surprised to see the announcement today,
I am sure everyone is surprised and has various feelings,
I am very sorry,
I am very sorry, but I want to convey my feelings and thoughts to all of you who are here today,
I would like to convey my thoughts and feelings as much as I can to those who have gathered here today.
Yes, that's right.
First of all, I would like to talk about why I quit the group and the Batten Show itself,
There were a number of things that came together,
The most important reason is that Sakura Seta, myself, has always been a bit ill,
I don't think I've told you guys much about this,
I haven't told you much about it, but there were times when I was prone to physical problems, and times when I felt a bit unstable,
I have been going through such a period for several years now,
I wanted to do my best in my activities, but my body just wasn't able to keep up.
I have been having a hard time keeping up with my body,
I can perform at the front shows, but I can't make it to the backstage,
I had a lot of problems in lessons and behind-the-scenes activities, even though I could make it to the front shows,
That's where I started,
I have been active as Batten Shoujo-tai since I was in junior high school,
I had only dreamed of being an idol,
I had a lot of dreams about what kind of idol I wanted to be and what kind of goals I wanted to achieve as a member of Batten Shoujo-tai,
I had a lot of dreams, but I couldn't keep up with them,
But I couldn't keep up with them,
But I couldn't keep up with them, and the situation was very difficult,
I had to find a goal or a dream for Sakura Seta as an individual,
I thought that I might regret my life if I didn't find some personal goal or dream,
I felt guilty.
I felt guilty, but it was hard for me to think about that since my fans have been supporting me so much and coming to see me every week,
It was hard for me to think about that, but I wanted to take my time for my future, and since I only had a dream of becoming an idol, I started by searching for my dream,
I started by searching for my dream.
I started from the beginning, and it took me quite a long time to find it,
After that was decided, I wondered if I could really go down that path,
I am very fulfilled when I have the potential to do so,
I was full of fun, and I had no hope for the future.
So I was very worried,
I made the decision to move on to a new path, and consulted with the office and the members,
I was still in a state where my feelings were firmly fixed, but I told them about it.
Yes, I have.
As for the group, I was not sure if quitting was the right thing to do,
I honestly don't know if it is the right thing to do, but I think I want to do my best,
But I will do my best.
Also, I will be leaving Standard Soft Promotion at the end of December,
The reason for this is that I think there are many kinds of entertainment activities,
I have been thinking that I would like to challenge myself while I was working as a batteress,
The first reason is that I belong to Batten Shoujo-tai,
I wanted to make Fukuoka, Kyushu, more exciting and to let people know more about Batten Shoujo-tai,
That is why I decided to quit Batten Shoujo-tai and work as an individual,
So, I couldn't see the vision of quitting Batten Shoujo-tai and working as an individual,
Therefore, I would like to leave Stalagt Promotion without any activities,
I have discussed this with my office.
That is all I have to say. Thank you very much.
I think that today's announcement of my graduation may have made everyone think that I no longer like being an idol.
I think I may have made you all think that I hate being an idol now that I announced my graduation.
I really love being an idol and find it very rewarding.
I really love idol activities and find them very rewarding.
I have never been able to continue like this before.
I've tried many things in my personal life and private life.
I've tried many things in my personal life and private life, but I've never been able to continue like this.
I was so encouraged by everyone's smiles and support for me to do my best.
I was so encouraged by their smiles and support for my efforts.
I've been working here since I graduated from high school.
I have been doing this job since I graduated from high school.
I've been working only with Batenshoue since I graduated from high school, and I've noticed that I've been working more and more.
I've realized how much I really appreciate
support from the people of the world.
is what makes me who I am.
Yes, that's right.
At first, I thought I wanted to do it with an ego, but it's really all about the members.
I don't know how to explain it, but...
I don't know how to tell you this, but my hobbies and private life are all Batten Girls Club,
I don't know how to tell you this, but my hobbies and private life are all Batten Girls Club members, and my life is made possible by the memories I have with the members,
I'm really afraid to leave this job or Batten Girls Club,
That's all I can do.
That's why I'm scared.
So I am scared and I feel sad,
I really feel sad, but since I started this job, I have received a lot of smiles from everyone,
I have received many smiles from everyone,
I am the type of person who is not good at smiling,
But I have received so many smiles from everyone,
I can always spend time with a smile on my face.
Everyday.
So, with the smiles that everyone has taught me
I want to do my best from now on.
I know I've said a lot and it's all a bit jumbled up,
I have really been able to run this far because of the fans, the members, the staff, and everyone,
Thanks to the fans, the members, and the staff, I have been able to run this far,
I have had a lot of support from the fans, members, and staff,
I have had a lot of potential, difficulties, and hardships,
There have been many difficulties and hardships, and there was even a time when I was in a quandary,
But because of your support, I have been able to come this far.
I was also able to find a new dream,
I am very happy to have been able to work as Battention itself,
I am very happy to have been able to find a new dream and to have been able to work as batention itself,
There are only 4 months left, just 4 months,
I am looking forward to meeting as many of you as possible and communicating with you as much as possible,
I'm looking forward to seeing many of you and communicating with you as much as possible.
I am looking forward to meeting many of you and communicating with you as much as possible. I would like to meet you at the live and at the benefit events and express my gratitude with a smile.
I am going to release Trizine this week as well,
I have many other events coming up, including the release event of Trizine and the fall tour from September to October,
We have many other events coming up, and finally, our graduation concert,
Finally, there will be a graduation live.
I am grateful for this opportunity,
I am grateful for this opportunity, and I have been told that they will prepare my intention for the graduation live,
I will do my best until the end.
I look forward to working with you for the remaining four months.
Thank you very much.
In case you are wondering, Ai-chan also speaks.
You use it too, Ai.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure how I feel about it yet,
YashikiI miss you a lot,
I wish we could still see each other together,
But I've seen Sakura working so hard, and I've been close to her,
I've seen Sakura working so hard and I've been close to her,
I'm sure there are many things you don't know about her.
It took a lot of courage to find your dream.
I think it took a lot of courage to find your dream.
And I think it's great that you told me that.
I'm sure our dreams won't be the same from now on.
We may be aiming at different places, but I hope we can work hard together.
I will always support you and I hope we can make a lot of memories and have a good time in the remaining 4 months.
Thank you so much.
I've been through this so many times...
I think it's better to have as few experiences like this as possible,
I think it is better to have as few of these experiences as possible, but I still feel that I am not used to it,
I'm sure that many of you are probably surprised right now,
I know some of you are probably too surprised to watch this distribution, and some of you may not be able to watch it with much feeling,
But when Sakura told me that she wanted to talk to me, I thought, "Don't tell me, don't tell me,
When Sakura told me she had something to say, I thought, "Please don't say it, please don't say it,
In fact, it was a decision until today's official announcement,
I was thinking that they might say that today's announcement had been cancelled, even though it had been decided until today,
And here I am now,
Sakura has brought so much influence and power to this group,
Of course I'm scared of losing that,
Of course I'm scared of losing her, and I wish we could have continued to work together as 6 members,
But Sakura still thinks about Batten Shoujo-tai so much,
All the members and the members of the group know that,
I think all the members understand that, so we also feel sad that Sakura has made this decision.
We don't tell you not to feel sad, so we hope that you will still support Sakura as she is.
I hope that we can support Sakura and the other members, and we can all support each other,
I don't know if the remaining 4 months are long or short,
I don't know if it's a long time or a short time, but I'm sure we'll have many chances to meet Sakura,
There are many chances to meet Sakura, so I hope that you will come and send her your appreciation and encouragement,
I hope that you will come to see Sakura and send your appreciation and encouragement to her, and at the same time, I hope that we will do our best to make you feel happy for supporting Watential Corps.
I hope you will continue to support the six of us. Please continue to support the six of us.
I'm standing here for a moment after hearing from Sakura,
I thought I had accepted it and thought it was fine, but when the day came for me to tell you all about it, I just couldn't believe it,
But now the day has come for me to share it with you,
But when the day came to share it with you all, I read your writings and saw your, you know, reactions,
I was thinking that I had accepted it, but when the day came for me to present it to you all, I read your writings and saw your, uh, reactions,
I also felt as if I had not fully accepted it yet,
Well, I don't know, we have been working together for more than 9 years as Batten Girls' Troupe, and now Sakura is going to graduate.
Sakura is graduating.
I'm still a little anxious about that,
Sakura has made her own choice to graduate and to go on to her new dream,
And the 5 of us have chosen to continue the group as Batten Shoujo-tai,
I think the members of the group will also make choices such as to support the group for the next 4 months or to continue to support Batten Shoujo-tai in the future,
I am sure that they will make various other choices as well,
I am sure that you will make many other choices, but I don't know if they are the right ones yet,
To be honest, I don't know if it is the right decision or not,
But I think everyone feels that this decision was the right one,
For us, for Batten Girls' Club, and for Sakura,
I hope that we, Batten Girls Club and Sakura can look back and think that it was the right decision,
I would like to move forward from now on,
I would like to look back and think that it was the right decision for us, Batten Girls Brigade and Sakura, too,
I would like to be able to look back and say, "I'm glad I supported Batten Girls' Club,
I would like to move forward without denying what we have done and what we will do in the future, making all of it right.
We will only be active for 4 more months as the 6 of us, but I hope you will continue to support us in the future as well.
I look forward to your continued support.
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's all right,
I would like to talk about our activities for the next four months, or rather, for the future.
First of all, the fall tour.
Tickets for the fall tour will go on sale tomorrow, Thursday, August 8, at noon.
The title of the tour is "Batten Girls Tour 2024 Tri! so that's what it is,
The venues, as previously announced, are ZEPP Shinjuku, Tokyo on September 7, and Indonesia on September 14, 15, and 16.
This one is a bit irregular, as the official fan tour ends tomorrow, August 8, at noon,
On the contrary.
If you are thinking of applying for this one, please hurry up and don't forget to do so.
The next stop is Cube Garden in Hokkaido on September 23, followed by Sendai Downwind in Miyagi on September 28, Gorilla Hall Osaka on October 5, and ZEPP Fukuoka on October 19.
Yes, I am going to be at ZEPP Fukuoka on October 19.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, wrong.
Six.
We will be touring for two months, so please come and visit us.
Please come and visit us.
The title of this show is pretty cool, so I'm working hard on it,
It's an alphabetical name, "Haraaay! is now a letter of the alphabet, isn't it?
Yes, it is. I've been saying "Halá'í! and it was called "Longer Upper Tour" or something like that,
There is less Japanese and more alphabet and live performance,
I would like to know what kind of live show it will be,
Of course I want those who have been supporting us to see the show,
Of course, I would like those who have supported us in the past to see what kind of live show we are going to do,
I think this is a good opportunity for those who have never been to the show or who have been wondering about it to come and see us,
So, I would like you to sign up for the tour.
So I would like to ask you to sign up for this event.
Please do so.
And, yes, I have already mentioned something about this,
Yes, and as I mentioned a little while ago,
We are going to have a graduation performance of Sakura Seto.
On Friday, November 29th, at Kaltz Kawasaki in Kanagawa,
And on Saturday, December 7, we will be performing at United Labo in Fukuoka.
I really didn't expect that they would prepare a graduation show like this,
I am very happy to be able to do this, but at the same time, I am very grateful for everything that you have given me,
I am very happy, but at the same time, I would like to repay you all for everything you have given me.
This will be the last concert for the six of us,
I hope you will come to see us and take home with you the good and the beautiful things about us,
I hope that you will come and see the show and take home with you the good and wonderful things about each one of us.
Please wait a little for the details and ticket information.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
We, Batten Shoujo-tai, are moving on to a new stage.
To connect Kyushu with the whole country and the whole world.
To become bigger and bigger as a group, to see more wonderful scenery with Mr. Tani,
We are holding an audition for new members to pursue our dreams with us.
We are very much looking forward to receiving many applicants.
I know it takes a lot of courage to apply for an audition,
We are looking forward to seeing new people who are willing to work together with us,
We are looking forward to having you join us. We are looking forward to your application.
I, Lira, am an idol.
Before I joined Batten Shoujo-tai, I was just a normal girl living a normal life,
But now that I have become an idol as a member of Batten Shoujo-tai, I have been able to see many wonderful sights with them,
I am very happy to be able to see so many wonderful sights with them and experience things I have never experienced before every day,
I wonder what it's like to be like that.
I think there is an organic audition or something like that,
I would like to go with them to see their dreams and goals together, and I would like to go with them to see the scenery,
I would like to go there with you,
I would love to become an idol,
I would like to be an idol, and I would like to work together with you.
I hope that those who are interested in becoming an idol or want to work together with us will apply.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I, Sakura Seta, am graduating from the group,
Sakura Seta is graduating from the group, so we have decided to hold an audition.
Yes, it's something about Patension itself,
They are a really wonderful group, and their music is really elaborate,
They have really elaborate songs, and they can try various genres,
And there was a place where I could learn how to sing and dance,
And there was a place where I could learn how to sing and dance, and where I could work hard with the members in a friendly competition,
I have been a member of this group for 9 years,
I have been active for 9 years, and every day has been a lot of fun, even though I know there are difficulties in being an idol,
I hope that many people will take on this challenge because it will truly change your life.
Before I became an idol, I was a very negative person,
If I had lived my life with a negative attitude, I think my life would have changed,
If I had lived my life as it was, I would have changed my life, but I didn't think I would have had such fun.
But now that you have entered the Batention Era
Yes, every day is fun.
I have found many wonderful things in the members of the team.
I have an environment where I am able to share my love with them.
I've never been in a profession where so many people have given me the opportunity to share their love.
I think that there is no other profession than being an idol that can do that.
I believe that the Batten Shoujo-tai team will support us,
I hope you will challenge Batten Shoujo-tai,
I hope you will challenge Batten Shoujo-tai to make idols and life more enjoyable.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, at first, as soon as I joined the office,
I thought I would never be able to stand up in front of people and sing and dance,
But once I got up on stage and danced and sang in front of everyone,
But once I got up on stage, danced and sang in front of everyone, and saw the smiles on their faces,
I thought, "Oh, how wonderful it is to be an idol," and I was fascinated by that,
I was fascinated by it.
I wanted to expand the circle of idols even further, and that is why I continue to be an idol today.
Something about making the people around me smile,
I also want to be an idol,
I think it is a very wonderful thing to be able to make someone smile through yourself,
I think it is a very, very wonderful thing to be an idol.
Of course there are hardships,
But the fun, satisfaction, and happiness I get from it outweighs the hardships.
If you are willing to work towards that goal with us, please apply for the audition and join us,
If you are willing to work towards that, I would be very happy if you would apply for the audition and join us. Thank you very much.
This is the first time Batten Girls' Choir is holding an audition.
I think it is almost a miracle that the eight members are here without having held an audition to join the group before,
I think it takes a lot of courage to challenge an audition,
The power and energy that come through the audition process is not necessarily limited to what is out in the world,
I think that if we could get girls who have hidden power and energy within us, Battin Shoujo-tai would be able to go a little higher.
I feel that it would be great if we could meet someone like that, and that's exactly what we, the Battin Girls' Corps, are looking for,
I think the members of the Battin Shoujo-tai know us and we know them the best,
We are not what is often called "royal road idols," but we are still idols,
We create a space of smiles with you and your fans.
We would like to challenge ourselves together with those who are interested in such things and who love Batten Shoujo-tai, Kyushu and Fukuoka.
We are looking forward to working with those who are not yet brave enough to join us,
We hope to be involved in the audition process together with them,
We hope to be involved in the audition process together with you.
We are not looking for anyone to replace anyone else, as has been the case with Lil' Min,
We are looking forward to having new members who can bring a breath of fresh air to the group,
We are looking forward to hearing from you,
We are looking forward to receiving many applications.
We have been able to come this far because of the support of all of you,
We have been able to come this far because of the support of so many people,
We are here now because of the support of many people,
I am here now because of the support of so many people.
We are all friends who are going to work hard together from now on,
I really love the stage,
I love singing and dancing,
I hope that the new members will feel that joy as well,
I hope that the new members can feel that joy and think that they like it, too.
I would like to grow even bigger, and I would like to see even more wonderful scenery with everyone who supports us, the members, and the staff. I am looking forward to working with you all.
I hope you will check out the details of the audition on the official website of Batten Shoujo-tai at 9:00 p.m.
Our current six-member group will be ending on December 7,
It would be a bit strange to say that we have been... more than that.
I think it's a little strange to say "more than ever".
I hope we can continue to perform on stage with gratitude to our members as before.
And of course, the new Batten Girls' Troupe will start new activities during the 4 months Sakura will be with us,
Which...
I hope that we can be seen by many people as Batten Shoujo-tai. Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much for your support.
Now that I've said all that, I'm sure you are all still feeling a bit unsettled, but since this will be archived, you can watch it over and over again,
I hope that you will look back on this archive as many times as you like and finally start to feel a little more willing to support us,
Of course, we have events in Nagoya and Osaka this weekend as well,
I hope you will come to see me at the events in Nagoya and Osaka this weekend as well,
There are many events until the end of August,
We have a lot of events until the end of August, and we will start our tour in September,
We are looking forward to seeing you all.
So, thank you all very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, we are Battenshon Style!
See you this weekend.